<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>in-depth on robertradi</title><link>https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/categories/in-depth/</link><description>Recent content in in-depth on robertradi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/categories/in-depth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kubernetes Service Accounts and Service Account Token Volume Projection</title><link>https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/posts/kubernetes-service-account/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/posts/kubernetes-service-account/</guid><description>If we want to use our Kubernetes cluster we have to talk to the Kubernetes api-server. But who is we? How does the api-server know who is talking to him? If no information provided then the api-server handles the request as an anonymous request. We do not want to allow an anonymous person to do anything in our cluster. That&amp;rsquo;s why we care about authentication in Kubernetes.
Basics There are two types of users is Kubernetes:</description></item><item><title>Everything you should know about Azure Managed Disks</title><link>https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/posts/azure-disk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/posts/azure-disk/</guid><description>One way to store data in Azure is using Azure Managed disks. Furthermore, disks will host your operating system. In this article, I am trying to give an in-depth look into Azure Disks.
Basics disks are independent first-class resources, meaning they can live on their own. This was not always the case, because at the beginning disks were a part of storage accounts. So, limits of storage accounts had to be taken into consideration.</description></item><item><title>Effect of externalTrafficPolicy on Kubernetes services</title><link>https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/posts/external-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://radirobi97.github.io/personal-website/posts/external-post/</guid><description>Just to be on the same page Kubernetes is all about containerization. Every container is placed inside a POD. The scheduler places the PODs onto different nodes. Nodes are the physical/virutal machines. A POD can have one ore more replicas by using ReplicaSet. There are no guarantees for that the PODs of the same ReplicaSet will be hosted on the same node.
How does the external traffic reach the destination POD?</description></item></channel></rss>